Guide to the Kenneth Hubbard Collection of Presidential Campaign Ephemera, 1840-2016 and undated RL.00580
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- 1928 Campaign
  - Smith, Alfred Emanuel, 1928
    - Button with printed photograph of Smith and text: Smith For President/I gave 1.00 Won't You?, 1928 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-ALS1928-002)
    - Button with printed photograph of Smith and text: Smith For President, 1928 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-ALS1928-003)
    - Pin portrait of Smith, black and white. Words: For President Alfred E. Smith, 1928 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-ALS1928-004)
    - Pin portrait of Smith, black and white. Surrounding red white and blue pattern, 1928 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-ALS1928-005)
    - Pin red white and blue, words: Smith and Robinson, 1928 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-ALS1928-006)
    - Pin red white and blue, words: Smith and Robinson, 1928 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-ALS1928-007)
    - Pin portrait of Smith, black and white. Words: For President Alfred E. Smith, 1928 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-ALS1928-008)
    - Pin portrait of Smith, surrounding red white and blue. Words: Smith for President., 1928 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-ALS1928-009)
    - Copper pin portrait of Smith, words: For President Alfred E. Smith, 1928 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-ALS1928-010)
  - Thomas, Norman Mattoon, 1928
    - Socialist Party Platform, 1928 (Box 13)
- 1932 Campaign
  - Garner, John Nance, 1932
    - Pin with black border and printed photograph of Garner, with text: Garner for President, 1932 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-JNG1932-001)
  - Hoover, Herbert Clark, 1932
    - Pin gold with profile portrait of Hoover with text: Herbert Hoover 1932 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HCH1932-001)
    - Pin gold with profile portrait of Hoover with text: Herbert Hoover 1932 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HCH1932-002)
    - Pin red and blue, with text: Speed recovery re-elect Hoover, 1932 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HCH1932-003)
    - Pin red and blue, with text: Speed recovery re-elect Hoover, 1932 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-HCH1932-004)
    - Pin red and blue, words: Speed Recovery Re-Elect Hoover, 1932 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-HCH1932-001)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, 1932
    - Badge with coin with profile of Roosevelt and text: Inauguration March 4, 1933, Lucky Tillicum, Rebuild with Roosevelt, Prosperity, Follow the Roosevelt Trail (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR1932-001)
  - Thomas, Norman Mattoon, 1932
    - Socialist Party literature, 1932 (Box 13)
- 1936 Campaign
  - Landon, Alf Mossman, 1936
    - Republican Party platform, speeches, campaign literature, 1936 (Box 13)
    - Blue GOP elephant pin, yellow flower with elephant trinket. Words: Landon Knox., 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-001)
    - Pin with sunflower, blue background, words: Landon., 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-002)
    - Pin with sunflower, white background, words: Landon Knox, 1936 in middle. (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-003)
    - Pin with sunflower, brown background, words: Landon and Knox., 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-004)
    - Pin portrait of Landon, black and white, American flag background. Words: Landon for President., 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-005)
    - Pin GOP elephant, brown background, words: Landon Knox. Yellow flower behind pin, 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-006)
    - Pin blue and white, words: Landon Deeds Not Deficits., 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-007)
    - Pin with sunflower, sepia portrait of Landon., 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-008)
    - Pin brown, word: Landon. Yellow cardboard flower behind pin., 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-009)
    - Metal elephant pin, words: Landon & Knox., 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-010)
    - Pin red white and blue, words: Off The Rocks with Landon and Knox., 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-011)
    - Pin portrait of Landon, black and white, American flag background. Words: Landon for President., 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-012)
    - Pin portraits of Landon and Knox, names printed under, GOP elephant. Metal framing, bird on top, 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-013)
    - Pin with sunflower, black and white portrait of Landon, name printed under. White background, 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-014)
    - Pin with sunflower, brown background. White strip, words: Landon Volunteers., 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-015)
    - Pin with sunflower. White strip, words: Americans Cannot Be Bought, 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-016)
    - Small pin GOP elephant, words: Landon Knox. Yellow flower behind pin., 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-017)
    - Pin with sunflower, words: Landon. Yellow flower behind pin., 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-018)
    - Big pin yellow blue and red, sunflower outside. Words: We Can't Eat Sunflowers, Disgusted Republican Let's Lose with Landon., 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-019)
    - Pin portrait of Landon, black and white, American flag background. Words: Landon for President. Small white elephant trinket., 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-020)
    - Pin with sunflower, portrait of Landon black and white, name printed under. Metal framing, bird on top., 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-021)
    - Pin portrait of Landon, black and white., 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-022)
    - Blue pin, words: Democrat for Landon., 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-023)
    - Pin with sunflower, white background. Words: Landon and Knox., 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-024)
    - Pin with sunflower, white background, words: Landon Knox, 1936 in middle. (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-025)
    - Pin portrait of Landon, black and white, words: For President Alfred M. Landon, 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-026)
    - Pin portrait of Landon, black and white., 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-027)
    - Pin portrait of Landon, black and white. Gold frame., 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-028)
    - Small pin with sunflower, white background, words: Landon Knox, 1936 in middle. (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-029)
    - Pin GOP elephant, brown background, words: Landon Knox. Yellow and black flower behind pin, 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-030)
    - Pin portrait of Landon, black and white, name printed under. White background, sunflower around portrait., 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-031)
    - Metal pin, small metal portrait of Landon, name printed under, red white and blue around portrait., 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-032)
    - Sunflower pin, copper center, word: Landon., 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-033)
    - Small pin with sunflower, white background, words: Landon Knox, 1936 in middle. (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-034)
    - Blue pin, word: Landon, red 5., 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-035)
    - Sunflower pin, metal elephant in center, 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-036)
    - Pin, blue and white, words: Landon Deeds Not Deficits, 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-037)
    - Rectangle pin, chipped blue and gold, word: Landon, 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-038)
    - Small metal sunflower pin, words: Landon Knox, 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-039)
    - Small rectangle pin, blue, words: Landon Knox, sunflower in middle, 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-040)
    - Pin portrait of Landon, black and white, name printed under. White background, sunflower around portrait., 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-041)
    - Pin portrait of Landon, black and white, white enamel sunflower around portrait, 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-042)
    - Metal sunflower pin, yellow 1 in center, 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-043)
    - Small pin GOP elephant, brown background, words: Landon Knox, 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-044)
    - Pin with sunflower, brown background, words: Landon and Knox., 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-045)
    - Blue tag, words: Veteran, Landon Bricker, 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-046)
    - Tag red white and blue, words: Landon Knox in blue, 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-047)
    - Tag red white and blue, words: Landon Knox in blue, 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-048)
    - Tag red white and blue, words: Landon Knox in red, 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-049)
    - Sunflower tag, words: Landon and Knox, 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-050)
    - Pin with sunflower, brown background, word: Landon, 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-051)
    - Metal pin with liberty bell, words: Landon (red) Liberty (white) and A New Prosperity (blue), 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-052)
    - Copper coin or button, portrait of Landon, words: For President Alf M Landon, 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-053)
    - Metal sunflower pin, portrait of Landon in center, name printed over, 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-054)
    - Pin GOP elephant, brown background, words: Landon Knox. Yellow sunflower behind pin, 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-055)
    - Pin white and blue, words: Victory Landon. Yellow sunflower behind pin, 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-056)
    - Pin red white and blue, words: Elect Both Landon Doutrich, 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-057)
    - Pin GOP elephant, brown background, words: Landon Knox. Yellow sunflower behind pin. White metal ribbon, words: Worker Young Republican of N.J., 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-058)
    - Small metal sunflower pin, words: Landon Knox, 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-059)
    - Metal sunflower pin, copper center, 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-060)
    - Pin sepia portrait of Landon, sunflower outside, white background. Large yellow sunflower behind pin., 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-061)
    - Pin black and white portrait of Landon, sunflower outside, white background. Large yellow sunflower behind pin., 1936 (Box 24, Item RL-00580-AML1936-062)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, 1936
    - Button with printed photographs of Earle, Roosevelt, and Lewis; text: Mitchell Day Oct. 29 1936 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-FDR1936-001)
    - Pin with American flag border and printed photograph of Roosevelt and attached plastic donkey and ribbon with text: Souvenir of Democratic National Convention Philadelphia June 1936 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR1936-002)
    - Pin with American flag emblems and printed photograph of Roosevelt and text: Inauguration 1937 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR1936-003)
  - Thomas, Norman Mattoon, 1936
    - Button with text: Guest Socialist Party 19th National Convention Cleveland O. May 1936 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-NMT1936-001)
    - Pin with ribbon and text: Alternate National Convention Socialist Party Cleveland May 23-26 1936 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-NMT1936-002)
    - Socialist Party Platform, 1936 (Box 13)
- 1940 Campaign
  - Aiken, John W., 1940
    - Socialist Party literature, 1940 (Box 13)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, 1940
    - Pin with American flag border and printed photographs of Roosevelt and Wallace and text: Roosevelt, Wallace, 1940 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR1940-001)
    - Pin with American flag border and printed photographs of Roosevelt and Wallace and text: Roosevelt, Wallace, 1940 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR1940-002)
    - Pin green, with text: better a third termer than a third rater, 1940 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR1940-003)
    - Pin white, with text: Two good terms deserve another, 1940 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR1940-004)
    - Pin white, with text: Two good terms deserve another, 1940 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR1940-005)
    - Pin white, with text: Force Franklin out at third, 1940 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR1940-006)
    - Pin white, with text: better a third termer than a third rater, 1940 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR1940-007)
    - Pen yellow, with text: Force Franklin out at third, 1940 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR1940-008)
    - Pin white, with printed photograph and Roosevelt and drawing of capitol building with text: Souvenir of the Inauguration Jan. 20th 1941, 1940 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR1940-009)
    - Pin yellow, with text: Lincoln didn't Washington wouldn't Roosevelt shouldn't, 1940 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR1940-010)
    - Pin white, with text: Strike three F.D. you're out, 1940 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR1940-011)
    - Pin white, with printed photograph and Roosevelt and drawing of capitol building with text: Souvenir of the Inauguration Jan. 20th 1941, 1940 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR1940-012)
    - Pin white, with corn image and text: Roosevelt Wallace, 1940 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR1940-013)
    - Pin with gold rim, printed photograph of Wallace, and hanging bar, with text: For Vice-President Wallace, 1940 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR1940-014)
    - Pin gray, with text: No. 5th Franklin gets his walking papers, 1940 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR1940-015)
    - Pin red with blue rim, with printed photographs of Roosevelt and Wallace, with text: Roosevelt Wallace, 1940 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR1940-016)
    - Pin with printed photograph of Roosevelt and plastic donkey and ribbon attached, with text: Roosevelt & Wallace Inauguration Jan. 20, 1941, 1940 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR1940-017)
    - Pin with American flag border and printed photographs of Roosevelt and Wallace with plastic donkey and ribbon attached, with text: Roosevelt & Wallace Inauguration Jan. 20, 1941, 1940 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR1940-018)
    - Yellow button with blue text: No 3rd Term the Constitutionalist, 1940 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR1940-019)
  - Thomas, Norman Mattoon, 1940
    - Socialist Party Platform, clippings, 1940 (Box 13)
  - Willkie, Wendell Lewis, 1940
    - Button with Uncle Sam graphic and text: No Third Term, 1940 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-001)
    - Pin with Willkie portrait and text: Willkie, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-002)
    - Pin with enamel ribbon, Willkie portrait, and text: Willkie, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-003)
    - Button with Willkie Portrait surrounded by small eagles, and text: For President Wendell L. Willkie, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-004)
      RL-00580-WLW1940-004 is a larger duplicate of the following RL IDs: 005
    - Button with Willkie Portrait surrounded by small eagles, and text: For President Wendell L. Willkie, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-005)
      RL-00580-WLW1940-005 is a smaller duplicate of the following RL IDs: 004 and 0031
    - Button with Sepia Willkie Portrait, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-006)
    - Gold Pin with ribbon and gold, bejeweled crown, and text: No Crown for Franklin, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-007)
    - Button with design of Uncle Sam Hat, and text: Willkie; minute man, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-008)
    - Button with portrait of young man surrounded by text: Every "Buddy" for Willkie, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-009)
    - Pin with text: No Man Is Good Three Times, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-010)
    - Pin with text: Good-Bye Mr. Third Term Candidate, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-011)
    - White button with Text: No Third Term, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-012)
    - White button with Text: No New Deal We Want A Square Deal, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-013)
      RL-00580-WLW1940-013 is a duplicate of RL IDs: 36
    - White button with Text: Boy Do We Need A Change!, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-014)
    - Yellow Button with Green Text: Willkie For President of CommonWealth and Southern, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-015)
    - Large Pin with text: Willkie or Bust, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-016)
      RL-00580-WLW1940-016 is a duplicate of RL IDs: 033
    - Small white pin with blue highlight, and text: Learn to say President Willkie, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-017)
    - Large White Pin with Text: White Plains for Willkie and McNary, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-018)
    - Pin with ribbon and black and white portrait of Willkie, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-019)
    - Button with text: Caution we need Willkie Not Dictatorship, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-020)
    - Button with portrait of Willkie and white elephant hanging from string, and text: Wendell Willkie, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-021)
    - Green Button with image of donkey, ribbon with hanging elephant, and text: I'll bet my... on Willkie, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-022)
    - White Button with text: I Am A Democrat For Willkie, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-023)
    - Large White Button with Dark Green Text: If I Were 21 I'd Vote For Willkie, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-024)
      RL-0058-WLW1940-024 is a duplicate of RL IDs: 035
    - White Button with Text: Willkie Says Spinach is Spinach It Sure Is Franklin, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-025)
    - White Button with Text: Put Back Private, Willkie in the White House, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-026)
    - Set of Matches featuring a portrait of Willkie and images of potential voters on each match, and text: We The People Want Willkie., 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-027)
    - White button with text: Willkie or Bust, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-028)
    - Blue Button with ribbon and anchor, and text: Two Good Terms Deserve A Rest, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-029)
    - Brown Button with portrait of Willkie, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-030)
    - Large Button with Portrait of Willkie surrounded by small eagles, and text: For President Wendell L. Willkie., 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-031)
      RL-00580-WLW1940-031 is a larger duplicate of RL IDs: 004 and 005
    - Mustard colored button with black text: Roosevelt Goodbye Hello Willkie, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-032)
    - Large Pin with text: Willkie or Bust, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-033)
      RL-00580-WLW1940-033 is a duplicate of RL IDs: 016
    - Yellow button with black text: I'll bet my [photo of donkey] on Willkie, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-034)
    - White pin with Black text: If I Were 21 I'd Vote for Willkie, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-035)
      RL-00580-WLW1940-035 is a duplicate of RL IDs: 024
    - White button with text: No More New Deal We Want Square Deal, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-036)
      RL-00580-WLW1940-036 is a duplicate of RL IDs: 13
    - White button with text: Wendell pitching Franklin Out, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-037)
    - Cyan colored button with black text: De-thronement day Nov.5th, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-038)
    - White button with blue text: Independent [Willkie] Volunteer, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-039)
    - White Pin with black text: Eleanor start packing, the Willkies are coming, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-040)
      RL-00580-WLW1940-040 is a duplicate of RL IDs: 41
    - White Pin with read border and black text: Eleanor start packing, the Willkies are coming, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-041)
      RL-00580-WLW1940-041 is a duplicate of RL IDs: 40
    - White button with purple text: No Royal Family, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-042)
    - Wooden medallion with ribbon and text: We Want Willkie, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-043)
    - silver button with blue text: Learn to say "Wendell Willkie", 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-044)
    - Orange button with black text: Thanksgiving day Nov. 5, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-045)
    - White button with blue text: Will [image of key], 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-046)
    - Pink button with navy blue text: Peace! Willkie Its Wonderful, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-047)
    - White button with pink text: Lucky Willkie, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-048)
    - White button with red border and blue text: Willkie [small insignia and #17], 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-049)
    - Button with red upper border, white middle, and blue lower border and text: Willkie for President, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-050)
    - Pink Button with portrait of Willkie and text: Wendell Willkie, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-051)
    - Button with stars and stripes design around the border, portrait of Willkie and text: Win with Willkie, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-052)
    - White button with text: Willkie, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-053)
    - White button with red border and text: We Want Willkie, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-054)
    - Red, White and Blue button with two white stars and text: The Lady on the other side is requested to vote for Willkie", 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-055)
    - Button with portrait of Wendell Willkie surrounded with stars and stripes and text: Wendell Willkie for President, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-056)
      RL-00580-WLW1940-056 is a dulicate of RL IDs: 58
    - Black and White portrait of Wendell Willkie surrounded by stars and stripes and banner with small elephant doll, 1940 (Box 19, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-057)
    - Button with portrait of Wendell Willkie surrounded with stars and stripes and text: Wendell Willkie for President, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-058)
      RL-00580-WLW1940-058 is a duplicate of RL IDs: 56 "larger elephant"
    - White button with text: The American (in red) with Willkie (in blue), 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-059)
    - White button with blue text: If I Were 21 I'd Vote for Willkie, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-060)
    - White button with green text: If I Were 21 I'd Vote for Willkie, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-061)
    - White button with light green text: If I were 21 I'd Vote for Willkie, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-062)
    - White button with green text: If I Were 21 I'd Vote for Willkie, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-063)
    - Red and Blue button with text: No Third Term, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-064)
    - Blue and White button with text: The Constitutionalists; No Third Term, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-065)
    - Mint colored button ith blue text: I won't make the same mistake again, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-066)
    - Mustard colored button with green text: Confidentially I'm voting for Willkie, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-067)
    - White button with red text: Washington Sweeptakes 1st Wendell 2nd Franklin 3rd Eleanor, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-068)
    - White button with blue text: If Willkie's in Whitehouse its US in Poorhouse, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-069)
    - White button with red border and text: No Fourth Term Either, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-070)
    - White button with green text: Out stealing third, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-071)
    - Orange button with black text: Eleanor start packing the Willkies are coming, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-072)
    - White button with blue text: Willkie you said a mouthful, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-073)
    - White button with text: The American Way (red text) with Willkie (blue text)., 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-074)
    - White button with image of key and text: Watch Will Win, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-075)
    - White button with blue text: I am a Willkie Democrat, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-076)
    - White button with green text: All I have left is a vote for Willkie, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-077)
    - light blue button with text: 99 out of 100 want Willkie why not me too, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-078)
    - Black pin with text: No third term, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-079)
    - Yellow pin with image of elephant trampling donkey and text: Down and out, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-080)
    - White button with blue text: My Friends Goodbye, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-081)
    - Blue button with blue text within white frame: My Friends Goodbye, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-082)
    - White button with green text: My Friends But Not My Subjects, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-083)